<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mixed Method Development of Evaluation Metrics</title>
    <link>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mixed Method Development of Evaluation Metrics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;#169; 2021. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abstract</title>
      <link>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/abstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/abstract/</guid>
      <description>Designers of online search and recommendation services often need to develop metrics to assess system performance. This tutorial focuses on mixed methods approaches to developing user-focused evaluation metrics. This starts with choosing how data is logged or how to interpret current logged data, with a discussion of how qualitative insights and design decisions can restrict or enable certain types of logging. When we create a metric from that logged data, there are underlying assumptions about how users interact with the system and evaluate those interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presenters</title>
      <link>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/presenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/presenters/</guid>
      <description>Praveen Chandar is a researcher at Spotify working on experimentation and evaluation of search &amp;amp; recommender systems. His research interests are in machine learning, information retrieval, and recommendation systems with a focus on experimentation and evaluation. Praveen received his Ph.D. from the University of Delaware, working on novelty and diversity aspects of search evaluation. He has published papers at top conferences including SIGIR, KDD, WSDM, WWW, CIKM, CHI, and UAI. He has also served as a program committee member at top conferences such as SIGIR, KDD, WSDM, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdd2021-mixedmethods.github.io/post/resources/</guid>
      <description> Mixed Methods for Evaluating User Satisfaction (RecSys 2018) Beyond Accuracy: Grounding Evaluation Metrics for Human-Machine Learning Systems (NeurIPS 2020) A/B Testing at Scale (SIGIR 2017, KDD 2017) Design for Searching and Finding (CHI 2015) Designing and Analyzing Large Scale Logs Studies (CHI 2011) Understanding &amp;amp; Inferring User Tasks and Needs (WWW 2018) Online User Engagement (KDD 2020)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
